(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-10T21:49:05.534103",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ラフィアンズ！
Ruffians!
フワワ・アビスガード、モココ・アビスガード
Fuwawa Abyssgard, Mococo Abyssgard
Are you ready? いくよー！
Are you ready? Here we go!
Nerissa Ravencroft
Koseki Bijou
Shiori Novella
Mori Calliope
Oozora Subaru
Ookami Mio
Aki Rosenthal
Shirakami Fubuki
AZKi
FUWAMOCO!
Ruffians!
It's showtime! 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime! I want to be with you!
Lifetime Showtime Anytime BAU BAU YAH
Future is bright Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
FUWA! MOCO! FUWA! MOCO!
FUWA! MOCO! BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU!
My heart n' soul n' tail are FUWAWA
I'm so fluffy that even I could float away
Just call for me, we're only a bark away
Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe
FUWA! MOCO!
I love being tricky, doggy kisses are for me
I love lots of walkies, don't need no leashes for me
Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere
FUWAMOCO together, take us along with you
Barking so merrily!
It's showtime! 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime! I want to be with you!
Lifetime Showtime Anytime BAU BAU YAH
一生涯 Sing with you
For a lifetime, sing with you
Stars wink Moon spotlight Furr-ever glow
It's showtime! 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime! I want to be with you!
Lifetime Showtime Anytime BAU BAU YAH
Future is bright Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Woo... BAU! Woo... BAU!
Way back then, all locked up, we were stuck in the cell
Holding back, doggy dog kept sealed away, BAU!
Bouta burst, fluff & fuss, we're meant to be free
Make a break for it, It's playtime!
Paws hitting the pavement
Dreams sparklin' within our eyes
Gonna keep you smilin'
But my sneezes won't stop flyin' by
Even though we're still just a pair
Just a pair of scaredy puppy dogs
The bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable
We're a pair unbreakable!
And that's why
いつだって It's that day!
Whenever, it's that day!
Today! Lifetime! Showtime!
Not tomorrow! BAU BAU!
一生涯 Walk with you!
For a lifetime, walk with you!
Good times and Bad times, It doesn't matter!
いつだって It's that day!
Whenever, it's that day!
Lifetime Showtime Everyday! BAU BAU!
Yeah, 二人は
Yeah, the two of us are...
Happy lucky puppy sisters!
FUWAMOCO BAU BAU!
Everybody BAU BAU!
Hallo hallo BAU BAU!
ダメダメノンノン! Don't touch the ears!
No no non-non! Don't touch the ears!
もふもふノンノン! Don't touch the tail!
Fluffy non-non! Don't touch the tail!
チワワじゃないよ! フワワだよ! BAU!
I'm not a chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa! BAU!
フワワじゃないよ! モココだよ! BAU!
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo! BAU!
Twin demon guard dog sisters, yeah! BAU!
And together, we're...
FUWAMOCO!
Gather up our dreams
And suddenly you'll come to realize
There's as many as there are stars
Illuminating the night sky
Never-ending dreams
We don't know if they all can be achieved
But we'll keep on going furr-ever
Together here with you!
It's showtime 一緒にいたい
It's showtime, we want to be together
It's showtime 一緒にいたいよ
Fuwa fuwa Moco moco Hand in hand with you
Bring your smile, rain or shine
We'll protect it Won't forget our pledge to you!
It's showtime 一緒にいたい
It's showtime, we want to be together
Lifetime showtime Anytime BAU BAU!
一生涯 Sing with you
For a lifetime, sing with you
Stars wink Moon spotlight Furr-ever glow
It's showtime 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime, we want to be together
Lifetime showtime Anytime BAU BAU!
And together, we're...
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Let's hear you!
いきますよー
Here we go!
FUWA! MOCO! FUWA! MOCO!
FUWAMOCO BAU BAU! FUWAMOCO BAU BAU!
Ruffians, BAU BAU!
Welcome to our FUWAMOCO Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival! BAU BAU!
Thank you so much for coming to celebrate our birthday with us! Yeah!
始まりましたー！
It has begun!
今日は配信ライブに来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming to our stream concert today!
Thank you!
So to continue off from yesterday's Friday show shenanigans...
Today, we have a big...
...concert! Can you believe it? It's already been three years!
Right! Our third birthday in hololive! Thank you!
But Moco-chan, we can't forget that really important thing, right?
Huh? Introductions?
Ah! Yeah! Okay!
I'm not a chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo!
We are hololive English -Advent-'s twin demon guard dog sisters!
Together, we're FUWAMOCO! BAU BAU!
And look!
We have an amazing Birthday Festival stage!
It's so big! Wow, Ruffians, it's so big!
And it's such a big full stage, too!
Fuwawa! Can we? Okay, here we go!
3, 2, 1, BAU BAU!
It's so big and wide!
Thank you all so much for being here today!
But singing and dancing today is not just gonna be us, right?
No, we're also here with some very special guests, too!
そう、今日はとっても素敵なゲストさんも来ているから、ぜひ楽しみにしてくださいね！
That's right, we have some wonderful guests joining us today, so please look forward to it!
そして、もう一人、謎のゲストさんも…？誰かな～？
And there's one more mysterious guest too...? Who could it be?
BAU BAU!
But a birthday wouldn't be complete without this, right?
I think you know it well, but...
Hashtag!
Yes! The birthday hashtag!
Right up here, you can see our birthday hashtag: #FWMCbday26! That it is!
Please, please post your thoughts, take lots of photos, screenshots...
ぜひハッシュタグで感想をつぶやいてください！写真もね！後でポチしに行くからね！
Please tweet your thoughts using the hashtag! Photos too! We'll go like them later!
We want to hear all your thoughts after the show!
BAU BAU!
Ah! Also...
We're going to be having a special membership-only concert right after this, so don't miss it, okay?
最後にはメンゲンのアンコールライブもありますので、ぜひ見に来てくださいね！
Finally, we'll also have a members-only encore stream, so please come watch!
Bau bau! Wow!
You know, in a concert after-party, should we get singing a little bit more, yeah?
For this next song, I think we need a special guest with us, right? Yeah! Let's call her on together!
For this next song, I think we need a special guest with us, right? Yeah! Let's call her out together!
Calli-senpai!
Hey hey hey! Ama-minasan! Bau bau!
Hey hey hey! Everyone! Bau bau!
Today only, I am also a dog. Shinigami dog!
Thank you for coming to our birthday! Thank you for inviting me! I'm happy to be here! What's up, Ruffians!
I see you have a pretty nice shirt there, hi! I do!
Look at this logo, what could it say? Check it out! Respectful! With respect! With respect!
It might be cute if we matched, right? Right! But maybe, why don't you go run and we'll get...
It might be cute if we matched, right? Right! But maybe, why don't you go run and we'll...
Can you entertain the Ruffians for a second? Yeah, okay! Entertain them!
Okay! You can do it! I got this. They won't bite. They won't bite. Okay! Bau bau!
Ruffians! Welcome to Mori Calliope's super special splits challenge segment! Ikuzo!
Ruffians! Welcome to Mori Calliope's super special splits challenge segment! Let's go!
I can't do it! I can't... I'm sorry, I can't do it! I did my best!
We're same size, right? Yeah! But I can't do that!
We're the same size, right? Yeah! But I can't do that!
We're matching! Triplet-ing! Triplet-ing? Has a nice ring to it.
And this next song is one that FUWAMOCO, we wanted to sing with you for such a long time!
And this next song is one that FUWAMOCO wanted to sing with you for such a long time!
Yeah! Something nostalgic! And I think you'll be able to see why. There's some rap as well. But it's also very cute, right?
次歌う曲は、Calli先輩と一緒にずーっと歌いたかった大好きな曲です！ね！
The next song we're singing is a song we love that we've wanted to sing with Calli-senpai for a long time!
It's both cute and cool! But I think, you know, it has an important part about, you know...
It's both cute and cool! But I think, you know, it has an important part about...
...you should be proud of what you like, right? An important meaning of being proud, being strong about what you like, yeah! Your likes!
...you should be proud of what you like, right? An important meaning of being proud and confident in what you like! Your likes!
Games, anime, idols, figures, or maybe even VTubers!
Nice sync there! After all, life is more fun when you're just true to yourself, right? Definitely! I agree! So we're going to sing this song for you, okay?
Okay, let me do the title call together, okay? Listen up! Like! Like! Like!
Okay, let's do the title call together, okay? Please listen: Like! Like! Like!
Comic, I Like it!
Music, I Like it!
Game, I Like it!
Animation, I Like it!
Figure, I Like it!
Movie, I Like it!
Wonder, I Like it!
Hobby, I Like it!
go go go go...
Do you like it? I Like it!
人生楽しんだモン勝ちの裏ワザ
The secret trick to winning life by enjoying it
好きなモノ好きって言えたらそれはスーパーノヴァ
If you can say you love what you love, that's a supernova
快感中枢即maxのover the sun
Pleasure center instantly maxed, over the sun
まるでギターかき鳴らし勝手に歌うバンドマン
Like a band member strumming a guitar and singing freely
plastic magic 回りくどくてゴメン 軸は一緒でしょ？
Plastic magic, sorry for being roundabout, but we're on the same page, right?
yes ! no reason キラメキな魂 今すぐlet's make sounds !
Yes! No reason, sparkling soul, let's make sounds right now!
キミが部屋に居たってlinkすればコンサート
Even if you're in your room, if we link up, it's a concert
いつだってonly, lonely... じゃあ手伸ばせ、行くよ
Always only, lonely... Then reach out your hand, let's go!
I like it ! like it ! スキになれば きっと全てがカラフルで
I like it! like it! If you fall in love with it, everything will surely be colorful
lucky ! lucky ! 星屑さえ、光る宝物さ
Lucky! lucky! Even stardust becomes a shining treasure
I like it ! like it ! キミに会えた、やっと「今日からヨロシクね」
I like it! like it! I could finally meet you, "nice to meet you starting today"
ホラ、キラキラ夢みたい 早く抱きしめたい
Look, sparkling like a dream, I want to hug you soon
アレもコレも欲しくて 神様に祈ってる
Wanting both this and that, praying to God
ねぇ 好きでしょうがない
Hey, I can't help loving it.
次は何にしようかな
What should I do next?
アールバックワンナイト 特丸愛を飛ばせ 音速ライク ライク Yeah
R-back 1-night, blast your special love at the speed of sound, like, like, yeah!
360度 パノラマ全方向 大好きの陣
360-degree panorama in all directions, the formation of big love!
何が愛等でもいいから 呑み込める 自分のアイテム like a superstar, fire, man
Whatever kind of love it is, take it in, my item like a superstar, fireman!
無敵アンディ 誇大泰然 来世
Invincible candy, grand and composed, next life!
望んでる誰もきっと現世が愛おしくなるはずなのさ
Everyone who desires it will surely come to cherish this present life!
成ろうとしてなるもんじゃない 人生楽しんでやるこっちゃない
It's not about trying to become something, it's about enjoying life!
自分に素直であれ
Be true to yourself!
スポットライト僕らを照らせ 今日も愛を叫ぶだけだ Get down!
Spotlight, shine on us! Today too, we just shout out love, get down!
I Like It! I Like It! 手を伸ばせば
I Like It! I Like It! If you reach out your hand...
きっと全てがミラクルで
...surely everything will be a miracle!
Happy! Happy! 日常でさえ
Happy! Happy! Even everyday life...
夢の物語さ
...is a dream story.
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I could meet you!
「ずっと、離さないでいてね」
"Keep holding on to me forever"
ホラ、キラキラ 虹みたい
Look, sparkling like a rainbow...
世界はまわりだす
...the world begins to turn!
好き好き好きでしょう 勝大 カルテに入れたい この感情 ハドメーター最高潮 真剣勝負
Like, like, you like it, right? Want to put this feeling in a chart, heart meter at its peak, a serious showdown!
ためらわないのがいいんでしょう?
It's better not to hesitate, right?
そう 恋はもう猛威と事件 でもそれが僕の等身大
Yes, love is already a rampage and an event, but that's my true self!
ガチですばらしい世界を確認 いわゆるひとつの萌え要素!
Confirming a truly wonderful world, so to speak, a moe element!
素直になれたなら Happy days
If you can be honest, happy days!
I Like It! I Like It! スキになれば
I Like It! I Like It! If you fall in love...
きっと全てがカラフルで
...surely everything will be colorful!
Lucky! Lucky! 星屑さえ
Lucky! Lucky! Even stardust...
光る宝物さ
...is a shining treasure!
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I could meet you!
「ヤッホー! 今日からよろしくね」
"Yoo-hoo! Nice to meet you from today on"
ホラ、キラキラ 夢みたい
Look, sparkling like a dream...
早く抱きしめたい
...I want to hug you soon!
I Like It! I Like It! 手を伸ばせば
I Like It! I Like It! If you reach out your hand...
きっと全てがミラクルで
...surely everything will be a miracle!
Happy! Happy! 日常でさえ
Happy! Happy! Even everyday life...
夢の物語さ
...is a dream story.
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I could meet you!
「ずっと、離さないでいてね」
"Keep holding on to me forever"
ホラ、キラキラ 虹みたい
Look, sparkling like a rainbow...
世界はまわりだす
...the world begins to turn!
Please listen to our next song! Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime!
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
[Song: Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime]
街角に並ぶ 映画のポスター
Movie posters lined up on the street corner...
もうこの街にも飽きたわ
...I'm already tired of this town.
受話器の向こうに ため息を返す 「キャンセルしないで...」
I return a sigh into the receiver, "Don't cancel..."
“Mon amour pour toi”
"Mon amour pour toi"
ハートのロケットに 隠した写真
A photo hidden in my heart-shaped locket...
誰も知らないホンキの恋
...a real love that no one knows about...
神様は気づいてる
...God notices it.
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime 叶わない夢なんて 見たくないわ
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime, I don't want to see a dream that won't come true...
でもロマンス 目覚めてゆく
...but romance is awakening.
“愛してるわ”
"I love you"
クレープに描く 愛の傘の下で
Under love's umbrella drawn on a crepe...
止まぬ雨の音 Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
...the sound of unceasing rain, Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime.
叶わない夜に
On unfulfilled nights,
支度はないから
because I'm not ready,
ほんの5分でも
even if it's just for five minutes,
会いたい
I want to see you.
キャンディショップも ネコショップも
Neither the candy shop nor the pet shop,
あなたがいないと
without you here,
つまらない
are any fun.
ジャケットのポケットに
In the pocket of my jacket,
入れたままのコインに
with the coin left inside,
賭けるわ 恋の行方
I'll bet on the fate of our love...
神様が知っている
Only God knows.
Je t'aime★Je t'aime
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
退屈な恋なんてしたくないわ
I don't want a boring romance.
あっという間に溺れてく
In an instant, I'm drowning in love.
“今がすべて”
"Now is everything"
カフェ・オ・レが冷めてしまうその前に
Before our café au lait gets cold,
もう一度KISSして
kiss me once more.
Je t'aime★Je t'aime
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
物語に
Locking up our story,
鍵をかけて
locking it away...
終日
All day long,
あなたのことばかりを夢見ている
I dream only of you.
もう何も Je t'aime★Je t'aime
Nothing else, Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime,
叶わない夢なんて見たくないわ
I don't want to see unfulfillable dreams.
でもロマンス目覚めてゆく
But romance is awakening.
“愛してるわ”
"I love you"
クレープに描く愛の傘の下で
Under the umbrella of love drawn on a crepe,
止まぬ雨の音
the sound of unceasing rain...
Je t'aime★Je t'aime
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
もう一歩
One more step...
退屈な恋なんてしたくないわ
I don't want a boring romance.
あっという間に溺れてく
In an instant, I'm drowning in love.
“今がすべて”
"Now is everything"
カフェ・オ・レが冷めてしまうその前に
Before our café au lait gets cold,
もう一度聞かせて
let me hear it once more.
Je t'aime★Je t'aime
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
La la la...
Wow! Look at that sunset!
Oh, it's setting already, huh?
Perfect timing!
Well, that last song was Je t'aime★Je t'aime!
What did you think, Ruffians?
It's a little bit more nostalgic, yeah, maybe even a bit melancholic!
You know, some city pop vibes, too!
Yeah! And the choreography was cute, too, right?
Right! We hope it made you feel nice, and all warm and fluffy-wuffy inside!
Yeah! With the sun setting now, it's starting to feel a bit romantic! Right?
Well, I guess it's the perfect time to call up our next guests!
Yeah! Here we go!
AZKi-senpai! Aki Rosenthal-senpai!
Happy Birthday!
Yay! Thank you! Welcome to the stage!
自己紹介をお願いします！
Please introduce yourselves!
はい！ こんこんあずき、AZKiです！
Hi! Konkon AZKi, I'm AZKi!
はい！ ホロライブ1期生のアキロゼことアキ・ローゼンタールです！
Hi! From Hololive 1st Gen, I'm Aki Rosenthal, aka AkiRose!
ポンパ！ ポンパ！ いらっしゃい！ ありがとうございます！
Ponpa! Ponpa! Welcome! Thank you so much!
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
AZKi先輩とアキロゼ先輩の歌声がすごく大好きなので、一緒にこの曲が歌えて...
We really love AZKi-senpai and AkiRose-senpai's singing voices, so being able to sing together...
次の曲に行って... そう！
Moving to the next song... yes!
アキ・ローゼン先輩とAZKi先輩はとっても魅力的なお姉さんたちなので
Since Aki Rosenthal-senpai and AZKi-senpai are such wonderfully charming, mature ladies...
あら！あらですか？
Oh my! Is that so?
ちょっとこの曲で行こうかなと思いました！
we thought we'd go with this song!
あらあら！
Oh my, oh my!
ちょっとね、日も暮れてますし...
You see, the sun is setting...
確かに！ちょっと夕方... ちょっとロマンチックになりましたね！
Indeed! It's getting to be evening... It's become a bit romantic!
実はちょっぴりセクシーかもー！
Actually, it might be a little bit sexy~!
セクシーかも？セクシーな曲？
A bit sexy? A sexy song?
お願いしたいことある？
Is there something you'd like us to do?
アキ・ローゼン先輩！えっと、この曲を歌う前に、少しあの、セクシーなウォーミングアップを...
Aki Rosenthal-senpai! Well, before we sing this song, a little... sexy warm-up...
教えてもらってもいいですか？いいですか？
Could you teach us? Would that be okay?
セクシーウォームアップ？オッケー！
A sexy warm-up? Okay!
じゃあ、まずセクシーな体を作るために...
Well then, first, to build a sexy body...
自分の体を撫でて...
stroke your body...
撫でて？
Stroke?
頭撫で撫で... 足から... 足から！
Patting your head... from the legs... from the legs!
撫でて... 撫でてみて？
Stroke it... try stroking it?
恥ずかしい！アキ・ローゼン先輩みたいに...
How embarrassing! Like Aki Rosenthal-senpai...
いいよ、いいよ！上手！
Good, good! You're doing great!
違う、違うよ〜！
No, that's not it~!
撫でるのがセクシー！足から... すごすぎる！
Stroking is sexy! From the legs... That's amazing!
も、もう一回！もう一回！
O-One more time! One more time!
ちょっと違うかな...
Maybe that's a bit different...
AZKiちゃんもなんかさ、セクシーだけど可愛い、ちょっと見せてよ！
AZKi-chan, show us something that's sexy yet cute too!
え〜？やっぱこうやって...
Eh~? I guess like this...
おー！かっこいい！凛と... あらあら！
Oh! So cool! So dignified... Oh my!
尻尾、尻尾！尻尾振りふり... 尻尾フリフリウォームアップ！
Tail, tail! Tail wagging... Tail-wagging warm-up!
プリプリプリプリ... オッケー、オッケー！
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle... Okay, okay!
いいんじゃない？いいよ、いいよ！
Isn't that great? Looking good!
できました〜！
We did it~!
じゃあ、いい感じになりましたね！
Well then, we're all warmed up now!
はい！次の曲に行きましょうか！
Yes! Shall we move on to the next song?
はい！じゃあ、聴いてください！
Yes! Well then, please listen!
DISCOTHEQUE!
CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA
DISCO LADY DISCO LADY DEEP EMOTION DEEP EMOTION
SWEETIE DARLIN' 踊りましょう
Sweetie Darlin', let's dance
はじける BEAUTY LADY
Popping beauty lady
生まれ変わって甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream
そっと彩りたいの
I want to softly color it
グラマラスな唇
Glamorous lips,
ピンク色の艶めくネイル
glistening pink nails
ガラスの向こう側に映る
Reflected on the other side of the glass,
素顔 シュールな Days
a bare face, surreal days
キミだけに SO 見せていたい
I want to show so much only to you,
心の中 瞳の奥
inside my heart, deep in my eyes
AH 傍にいて欲しいよ
Ah, I want you by my side
月の MIRROR BALL 照らされて
illuminated by the moon's mirror ball
MY DARLIN' ねぇ ヴィヴィッドな恋しましょう
My Darlin', hey, let's fall in vivid love
はじける SEXY BEAUTY
Popping sexy beauty
生まれ変わって甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream
そっと彩る MY LOVE
Softly coloring my love,
ほら 世界は変わる
look, the world is changing
CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA
SEXY FEELING CHU CHU... CHU CHU...
ドラマティックな情熱
Dramatic passion,
褪せない デジャヴ 見続けたくて
a fadeless déjà vu, wanting to keep watching it
カラフルな SWEET STORY
A colorful sweet story,
心深く 刻み込む
engraved deeply in my heart
小さな闇が 訪れても
Even if a small darkness visits,
恋の呪文 唱えたなら
if we chant the spell of love
そう、きっと 果てない空
Yes, surely, in the endless sky,
星屑の SHOWER が 降り注ぐ
a shower of stardust will pour down
だから HAPPY STATION 目指してゆこう
So let's aim for the Happy Station
50/50 あわせて
Combining 50/50,
100％以上の愛
love that's over 100%,
揺るぎなくここにあると
unwaveringly exists right here,
私思ってる
that's what I believe
CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA
ゆらゆら 渋谷交差点
Swaying at the Shibuya crossing,
ネガティブな自分
my negative self...
キミにありのままを
I want you to love me
好きでいてほしいと
just as I am,
願いを
making a wish...
素敵なら
If it's wonderful,
MY DARLING もっと一緒に踊りましょう
My darling, let's dance together more!
SECRET NIGHT 素敵な
Secret night, with a wonderful...
ラブソングのデコレーション
Love song decoration,
二人のハートリアレンジ 奏で合わせて
Rearranging our two hearts, playing in harmony...
MY DARLING ねぇヴィヴィッドな恋しましょう
My darling, hey, let's fall in vivid love!
はじける SEXY BEAUTY
Popping, sexy beauty!
生まれ変わって甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream,
そっと彩る MY LOVE ほら
gently coloring my love, look...
世界は変わる
The world is changing.
CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA
燃え尽きるわ この恋たぶん
This love will probably burn out,
どんな終幕が来ようと 覚悟してる
I'm prepared no matter what ending comes.
余裕なんて ほとんどない
I barely have any composure left,
必死でしがみついてるだけ
I'm just desperately holding on.
貴方の目
Your eyes,
優しく抱き寄せる腕
the arms gently pulling me close...
すべてが
Everything,
everything
初めての Fall in love だったわ
was my first time falling in love.
Kiss me 離さないで
Kiss me, don't let me go.
Kiss me 自然なままで
Kiss me, just naturally.
この不安を拭いとって
Wipe away this anxiety.
ねぇ...
Hey...
Touch me その指先
Touch me with those fingertips.
Touch me その眼差しで
Touch me with that gaze.
この私を包み込んで
Wrap around me...
Please...
愛してる
I love you.
よみがえるわ 昨日の事
Yesterday's memories come flooding back.
あんなに心が揺れたの 初めてだもん
It was my first time feeling my heart sway like that.
寂しすぎて 時に怖い
It's so lonely, sometimes it's scary—
二人で居れないこの時が
these moments when we can't be together.
雨の朝 暖かな部屋でコーヒー
A rainy morning, coffee in a warm room...
大人のフリから 本物の大人になれそう
From pretending to be adults, feels like we might become real ones.
Kiss me 危険な程
Kiss me to a dangerous degree.
Kiss me 甘い口づけ
Kiss me with a sweet kiss.
この願いを全部叶えて
Fulfill all of these wishes.
ねぇ...
Hey...
Knock me その魂で
Knock me with your soul.
Knock me 窓を叩いて
Knock me, knock on the window.
この私を安心させて
Reassure me...
Please...
愛してる
I love you.
Kiss me
行けないほど
So much that I can't leave...
Kiss me
甘いくちづけ
With a sweet kiss,
こんな願いを全部叶えてね
grant all of these wishes of mine, okay?
ねぇ
Hey...
Knock me
その魂で
with that soul of yours.
Knock me
窓を叩いて
knock on my window.
こんなわたしを安心させて
Put my mind at ease...
Please...
愛してる
I love you...
ワン、ツー！
One, two!
アイ・レディ？
Are you ready?
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
Please enjoy Triangle Dreamer!
day by day 日に日に募るの 乙女心
Day by day, a maiden's feelings keep growing.
同じクラス 斜め前の おとなしい人
That quiet boy sitting diagonally ahead in my class...
カッコ良くはないけれど 優しく いつも頼れる彼
He's not super cool, but he's kind and always reliable.
after school 恋愛相談の帰り道
After school, on the way back from talking about romance,
なんだって話せる親友の女の子
I'm with my best girl friend, who I can talk to about anything.
スポーツ万能 勉強もできて 女子力MAXです
Great at sports, smart in class, and maximum girliness!
どこにでもある よくあること
It's an everyday, totally common thing,
急に彼女が「あのね、実は私好きな人がいるの…！」って
when she suddenly says, "You know, I actually have a crush...!"
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, seriously!?
三角形 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Love triangles are so fickle,
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
and the balance crumbles in an instant.
ベタな漫画みたいなフラグ
It's a cliché plot point straight out of a manga.
まさかね自分が立てちゃうなんて 残念すぎます！
I can't believe I set off the flag myself—how embarrassing!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Love triangles are so unstable.
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's a category where "just kidding" won't cut it.
恋と友情 ゆらゆらめいて
Swaying between love and friendship,
なんか青春しちゃいます
I guess I'm living out my youth!
わたし 困っちゃいます
I'm totally at a loss!
乾杯です！ お似合いすぎるわ 勝てっこない
Cheers to them! They look way too good together, I can't win.
悔しいけど とかそんなんじゃなくて本心
It's not out of bitterness, I genuinely mean it!
てゆーか既に応援モード むしろすがすがしい
In fact, I'm already in cheering mode—it's actually refreshing!
だけど彼女は不思議な顔
But she gives me a strange look...
真剣な目で「そうじゃなくて、私あなたがスキ…ゴメン」って
With serious eyes, she says, "That's not it... I like you! Sorry..."
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, seriously!?
三角形 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Love triangles are so fickle,
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
and the balance crumbles in an instant.
わたし アナタ 彼女とわたし
Me, you, and her with me...
超絶！ 複雑！ 百合展開は想定外です！
Super complex! A yuri development was totally unexpected!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Love triangles are so unstable.
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's a category where "just kidding" won't cut it.
解けないパズル
An unsolvable puzzle...
与えたもうた
given to us by the heavens.
神よ 恨んじゃいます
God, I might just hold a grudge against you!
わたし
I...
悩んじゃいます
...am so confused!
あーもう！すごいヤバい！
Ah, geez! This is crazy!
好きだよ？好きだけど…って、そういう意味じゃなくって！
I like you, but... wait, that's not what I meant!
だって…女の子同士だし…
But... we're both girls...
ねぇ神様、どうしたらいいの？
Hey God, what should I do?
わたし、どうしたいの？
What do I want to do?
ヘルプミー！！！
Help me!
なんか変だー 愛に国境も歳も性別も関係ない！
Something feels off—love knows no boundaries, age, or gender!
けど、けど、けど！
But, but, but!
三角形 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Love triangles can be so fickle,
一瞬で 一瞬でくずれるバランス
losing balance in a heartbeat!
普通の恋 夢みてたのに
I dreamed of a normal romance,
ノーマル設定のわたしじゃ ちょっと無理ゲーすぎます！
but for normal old me, this game is way too hard!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Love triangles are so unstable!
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's way beyond a simple joke category!
彼女のこと 好きになれたら
If I could only fall in love with her...
なんて妄想しちゃいます
I catch myself daydreaming like that.
わたし どうかしてます
Something is definitely wrong with me!
いくよー！
Here we go!
Ruffians, thank you!
That was so much fun!
You're looking good, Ruffians!
How are you guys doing out here?
Thank you, Ruffians! That was so much fun!
Yeah, you know, I got a bit dizzy, though!
All the bubbles, and then changing so quickly!
That was so fast!
You know, that was a bubble dance! A little bit silly!
But did we surprise you?
And we got to see as well even more close-up than usual!
Wow! Those last two songs we sang was Kiss Me Aishiteru together with Aki-senpai...
Wow! Those last two songs we sang were "Kiss Me Aishiteru" together with Aki-senpai...
And Triangle Dreamer...
...with Fubuki-senpai, Mio-senpai, and Subaru-senpai!
What did you think, Ruffians?
Kiss Me Aishiteru, it's a song that I've always wanted to dance together with Aki-senpai!
"Kiss Me Aishiteru" is a song that I've always wanted to dance together with Aki-senpai!
Yeah, it's a little bit more sexy song!
Yeah, it's a little bit more of a sexy song!
Yeah, and Triangle Dreamer, the ultimate idol song!
The yuri development was so cute!
Are Ruffians still alive? Are you alive?
Aki-senpai was so cute in love!
Yeah! And crowd-surfing on the bubble!
Yeah, it was a first!
A lot of firsts this year, right?
Well, we have a tiny announcement!
You know, as FUWAMOCO, it's our birthday, right?
And so, we have something we'd like to share with you!
どーんどん！
Ta-da!
Bau bau!
It's time to celebrate both of our birthdays with the FUWAMOCO 2026 Birthday Set!
FUWAMOCOの生誕グッズ紹介、はじまり〜！
FUWAMOCO's Birthday Merch Showcase starts now~!
First, we became fluffy and fuzzy idols with the Fuwa Fuwa Idol Fuwawa...
...and Moco Moco Idol Mococo acrylic stands drawn by our mama, Ikomochi-mama!
They're a bit big compared to regular acrylic stands, so we think they'll be a great addition to your collection!
大きめサイズで可愛いアイドルのFUWAMOCOアクリルスタンド！
These big-sized, cute idol FUWAMOCO acrylic stands!
Next, we have the silly Ehehe Angel and Hoeh Devil rubber figurines!
They're palm-sized figures, perfect for displaying on your desk!
手のひらサイズのFUWAMOCOが手のひらサイズのラバーマスコットになったよ！
FUWAMOCO turned into palm-sized rubber mascots!
This one is big! We finally have FUWAMOCO plushies in our out-and-about casual outfits!
But this time, we also speak to you, Ruffians!
But this time, they also speak to you, Ruffians!
It's the Yappy Puppy Fuwawa/Mococo Sounds Plushies!
They'll be the same size as the Friends With You plushies, so you can display them together!
「おしゃべりばびー☆MOCOCOぬいぐるみ」のフワモコだよー！
We're the "Talking Baby MOCOCO Plushie" Fuwamoco!
ぎゅっとすると色々喋るよ！
When you squeeze us, we talk!
どんなボイスが出るかお楽しみに！
Look forward to seeing what kind of voices come out!
We have the Fuwawa to GO☆ Finger Puppet!
They both come with one extra Ruffians kigurumi costume you can dress us up in, and bring around with you everywhere!
FUWAWA to GO☆ 指パペット！
FUWAWA to GO☆ Finger Puppet!
どこでも一緒に連れていけるサイズで、着せ替えラフィアンズ衣装もあるよ！
They're a size you can take anywhere, and there's also a dress-up Ruffians costume!
By the way, we have two different ASMR voice packs: "Back from a Fluffy Date" with Fuwawa...
...and "Sweet and Fuzzy Needy Puppy" from Mococo!
ASMRボイスは英語と日本語両方で収録してます！
The ASMR voice packs are recorded in both English and Japanese!
Nemiru's heart beats so fast!
Be ready to blush when you take a listen to them!
The merch is separated into two sets: Fuwawa's Birthday Merch and Mococo's Birthday Merch!
If you purchase the full set, they come with bonuses, including a Cheki-style card with a special bonus voice!
グッズはフワワセットとモココセットに分かれています！
The merch is divided into Fuwawa and Mococo sets!
セットごとにチェキ風カードと特典ボイスがつきます！
Each set comes with a Cheki-style card and bonus voice!
The regular version will have a foil-stamped replica signature and message, so it'll be just as cute!
数量限定セットは直筆サイン付きだよ！
The limited quantity set comes with a handwritten signature!
We put lots of love into each and every signature, so we hope you look forward to it!
たくさんの愛情を込めてサイン書きますね！
We'll put lots of love into signing them!
Please check out the hololive official online shop and look for the link in the description or comment area!
Okay!
ぜひホロライブ公式ショップにチェックしてください！
Please check out the Hololive official shop!
BAU BAU!
What did you think of our birthday merch? Pretty cute, huh?
Well, the reservations will be going on sale right after the birthday live here ends! So don't forget, okay?
生誕グッズの予約はこの後開始しますので...
Reservations for the birthday merch will start right after this...
...お忘れずにチェックしてくださいね！
...so don't forget to check it out!
You can click the link below or on the side here! Don't forget, okay?
We put a lot of love into it, and Iikomochi... thank you Iikomochi mama!
Right after this ends, time to go go go, okay? Go buy it!
We've performed a lot of special collabs with a lot of dear senpais!
But there's still one mystery guest we haven't met yet, right?
まだ会ってない謎のゲストが1人いるんだよね！
There's still one mystery guest we haven't met yet!
Shall we give the Ruffians a hint, Mococo?
Ruffians, you're curious, right?
Could it be... YAGOO-san? YAGOO-san?
That's a good guess, maybe!
Well, you'll see!
Maybe you should get ready...
...because, you know, they aren't quite as bad as Peroco...
...but they can get pretty nasty sometimes!
Mococo-chan, you're not going to be rude to our next guest or anything, right?
Especially before calling them out!
We'll see!
Let's get them out here then!
Could it be? Could it be?
Okay! せーの...
Okay! Ready, set...
どうぞー！
Here they come!
わー！来たしんよ、来たしんよ！来たしんよ！あきんつー！
Waaah! I've arrived-shin! I've arrived-shin! I've arrived-shin! Akin-tsu!
ちゅ！ちゅ！ちゅ！
Chu! Chu! Chu!
自己紹介お願いします！
Please introduce yourself!
クロちゃんです！わー！
I'm Kuro-chan! Waaah!
クロちゃんしんよー！
Kuro-chan-shin!
初めまして！
Nice to meet you!
チワワじゃないよ！フワワだよ！
Not a chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
フワワじゃないよ！モココだよ！
Not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo!
2人合わせて...
Together we are...
...フワモコです！
...FUWAMOCO!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
フワモコのわちゃわちゃバースデーフェスティバルに来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to Fuwamoco's Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival!
Thank you!
ハッピーバースデーだしんよ！フワモコー！
Happy Birthday-shin, FUWAMOCO!
いい一年ね！
Have a great year!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ちょっとね、視聴者のラフィアンズはたくさんいると思いますけど...
Um, I'm sure there are many Ruffians watching right now, but...
...クロちゃんがどんな人なのか説明してもらえますか？
...could you explain to them what kind of person Kuro-chan is?
自分で描くの？それ！
I have to do it myself?!
そう！Introduction!
Yes! Introduction!
分かったしんよ！だってこれ海外の人も見てますもんね？
Got it-shin! Because overseas fans are watching too, right?
海外の人でも分かる自己紹介しますからね！
I'll do an introduction that overseas fans can understand!
Nice to meet you! Nice to meet you! Chu! Chu! Chu! Chu! Chu-lip!
Ah... Ow...
困らないで！
Don't look so troubled!
え、クロちゃんは... え、チューリップ？
Wait, Kuro-chan is... a tulip?
いや、チューリップ No No No No!
No, tulip No No No No!
ちょっとまだ分からないかもしれないから...
They might not understand yet, so...
えーっとね、安田大サーカスっていうトリオを組んでる芸人さんで...
Well, I'm a comedian in a trio called Yasuda Dai Circus...
...あと豆柴の大群のプロデューサーもやってまして、作詞とかもしてます、クロちゃんです！
...and I'm also the producer for Mameshiba no Taigun and write lyrics. I'm Kuro-chan!
BAU BAU!
じゃあ今回は英語でお願いします！
Well then, please do it in English this time!
僕が？
Me?
Yes!
自分で？
By myself?
そんなこと急に言われたら... It's shy flower!
If you ask me so suddenly... It's shy flower!
言い訳はなし！
No excuses!
聞いてる人の話！
I'm listening to what you're saying!
英語... えっと、なんだろう... えっと...
English... Um, what is it... um...
Famous comedian!
And Idol Producer!
やってるしんよ！
That's what I do, shin!
できるー！
Impressive~!
クロちゃんテレビでよく見てるけど...
We see Kuro-chan on TV all the time, but...
ちょっとフワモコのペットのペロちゃんと似てるところがたくさんあるね！
you actually have a lot in common with FUWAMOCO's pet, Pero!
後ろの姿を見てください！
Look at him from behind!
似てる！そっくり！ペロです！
They look so alike! Exactly the same! It's Pero!
待って！丸いところだけが似てるんじゃない？
Wait! Isn't it just that we're both round?
それだけじゃない！
Not just that!
クロちゃんと似てるところは、嘘つきで、女の子好きで、いやらしい！
How you're like Kuro-chan is... you're a liar, you love girls, and you're perverted!
だからね、見た目で騙されないで！
So don't be fooled by appearances!
クロちゃんはそんなので大丈夫なの？と言われて...
Is Kuro-chan really okay being told all that...?
いやひどい！悲しくなってきた！え〜んえ〜ん...
That's so mean! Now I'm sad! Waaah, waaah...
えー！
Eh!?
全然人の言うこと聞かないよね、君たちは！
You two don't listen to a word anyone says, do you!
できれば... クロちゃんはペロのお友達になってくれませんか？
If possible... could Kuro-chan become Pero's friend?
えっ、フワモコの友達じゃなくてペロの友達なの？
Huh? Not FUWAMOCO's friend, but Pero's friend?
フワモコはクロちゃんとお友達になりたくないから！
Because FUWAMOCO doesn't want to be Kuro-chan's friend!
おかしくない、それ？ いやいや、気持ち悪いから！
Isn't that weird? No, no, because you're gross!
気持ち悪くない！マニアック受ける！ 違う！気持ち悪い、やっぱり！
I'm not gross! I have niche appeal! No! You're gross after all!
でもでも、モコちゃん... ちょっとやりすぎですよ！失礼です！
But Moco-chan... that's going a bit too far! That's rude!
もしペロと仲良くなってほしいんだったのなら、可愛らしく頼んだ方がいいんじゃない？
If you want me to get along with Pero, shouldn't you ask me nicely?
はあー！？ No!
Huh!? No!
しっかりとした否定！
Such a firm rejection!
けどペロ可愛いから仲良くなってもいいとは思ってるよ！
But Pero is cute, so I wouldn't mind being friends with him!
嬉しい！可愛くないけど、仲良くなってくれたら嬉しいかな！
Yay! He's not cute, but we'd be happy if you became friends!
感情がいろいろありすぎるのよ、本当に！
You have way too many mixed emotions, seriously!
まあまあ！クロちゃんって芸人さんだけど、アイドルになりたいんですよね？
Now, now! Kuro-chan is a comedian, but you want to be an idol, right?
そう、元々アイドルになろうと思ったのに騙されて芸人にさせられたから... アイドルは本当に夢！ドリーム！
Yeah, I originally wanted to be an idol, but I was tricked into becoming a comedian... So being an idol is my dream! Dream!
なんか悲しいな... かわいそう... でもドリームって大事ですから！
That's kind of sad... Poor thing... But dreams are important!
クロちゃんのドリームはアイドルなんだから、せっかくなら一緒に歌ってくれませんか？
Since Kuro-chan's dream is to be an idol, why don't you sing with us while you're here?
いいしんよ、いいしんよ！オッケーだしんよ！ 一緒に踊れるんだね！
Sure, sure! OK, shin! So we can dance together!
この曲ね！ ハードル上げないで！
This song! Don't raise the bar too high!
大丈夫ですよ！アイドルのプロデュースもやってるし！実力見せてよー！
It'll be fine! You even produce idols! Show us what you've got!
オッケーだしんよ！行くしんよ！
Okay, shin! Here I go!
すごく可愛い曲を一緒に歌いましょう！ 楽しみ！
Let's sing a super cute song together! I can't wait!
オッケー！
Okay!
じゃあ、一緒にタイトルコールしましょうね！ せーの！
Let's introduce the title together! Ready, set!
ちゅ、多様性。 多様性あんの！？
Chu, Tayousei. There's diversity!?
我愛你 酔いが醒めない
Wo ai ni, I'm so intoxicated
Oh, I need you 恋が醒めない
Oh, I need you, I can't snap out of love
お生憎様の慣れ果て察して
Pity what I've become, just read between the lines
無問題 破滅してみて
No problem, go on and ruin yourself
Hold me tight トラウマの味
Hold me tight, tasting of trauma
猛反対 お手 お座りでハイ♡報酬
Strongly opposed, sit and shake for your sweet reward♡
喉の奥がチクンチクン
A sting in the back of my throat
僕はドクンドクン
My heart's pounding loud
鼓動で孤独消してみせてよ
Make my loneliness vanish with your heartbeat
愛も恋も独裁して
Rule over all my love and affection
僕を独占して
Keep me all to yourself
このまま中毒になるまでチューしよう
Let me kiss you till we're both addicted
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
Get get get get on chu!
熱く とろけるくらいに 溢れた気持ちが
Overflowing emotions, hot enough to melt away
たまらないでしょ
It's irresistible, isn't it?
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
Get get get get on chu! Get on! Get on!
我愛你 無問題
Wo ai ni, no problem
Get get get on chu!
ポン・チー・カン 勝負はいつもトンチンカン
Pon, chii, kan—the game is always absurd
僕に言わせりゃ ちんぷんかんぷんだ
If you ask me, it's all complete gibberish
最後はロンでしょ？
In the end, it's a win, right?
もう何回？ 殺られればいい
How many times do I have to get destroyed?
Oh, one night 忘れられない
Oh, one night, unforgettable
終わんないで トキメキ 偏愛♥予習
Don't let it end, this heartbeat, prep work for my biased love.
喉の奥が チュンチュン
Deep in my throat, it's chirping away,
僕は ドクドク
and my heart is throbbing.
心臓ごと 引きずり出してみせてよ
Drag out my heart and show it to me.
きもちいいね 面倒くさいけど
It feels good, even if it's a hassle,
やっぱ 照れくさいけど
but as expected, it's embarrassing.
死ぬまで 忘れられない チュー しよ
Let me give you an unforgettable kiss till death.
いかれた街は ゾンビで溢れる
This crazy town is overflowing with zombies.
君は僕に 恋してる
You're in love with me.
ときめく胸に 繋がるロープを 引きなよ
Pull the cord connected to my fluttering heart!
行くよ！ Bet bet bet on! Bet on chu!
Here we go! Bet bet bet on! Bet on chu!
本気で狂えるくらいの 鬱々しさが
This gloominess that could truly drive one mad,
美しいでしょ
it's beautiful, isn't it?
Get get get on! Get on chu!
せーの ポン・チー・カン 終わんない
Ready, set! Pon, chii, kan, it never ends!
Get Get Get on chu!
ほらね 我愛你 無問題
See? I love you, no problem!
Get Get Get on chu!
わー！やったー！
Yay! We did it!
うまくいったしんよー！
It went so well, shin-yo!
ありがとう！よかったー！
Thank you! That was great!
頑張ったね、クロちゃん！
You worked so hard, Kuro-chan!
楽しかった！ありがとう！
That was so fun! Thank you!
えっとね、サヨナラする前に...
Um, before we say goodbye...
えっと、1個お願いしてもいいですか？
Can we make one request?
1個だけだしんやー！
Just one thing, shin-ya!
1個だけじゃーん！
Yeah, just one thing!
えっと、FUWAMOCOは魔界の番犬で...
Um, FUWAMOCO are guard dogs of the Demon World...
「バウバウ」よく言ってるんですけど...
...and we often say "Bau Bau," but...
クロちゃん、カメラに向かって、FUWAMOCOのように可愛い「バウバウ」してもらえますか？
Kuro-chan, could you look at the camera and give us a cute "Bau Bau" like FUWAMOCO?
えー！できるかしん...
Eh?! I wonder if I can do it, shin...
行くしんよー！
Here I go, shin-yo!
バウ！バウ！
Bau! Bau!
え〜、バウ？それがベスト？
Eh~ Bau? Is that your best?
もう一回！もっとやって！
One more time! Do it more!
バウ！バウ！
Bau! Bau!
か、可愛いかな...？
Is... is it cute...?
実はおもう1個やりたいことがあるんですけど...
Actually, there's one more thing we want to do...
さっきやりましたけど、FUWAMOCOはいつもやってる自己紹介があって...
Like we did earlier, FUWAMOCO always has a self-introduction we do...
できれば3人で一緒にやりたいです！
If possible, we'd like to do it together with all 3 of us!
あれ可愛かったからやりたい、クロちゃんも！
That was cute, so Kuro-chan wants to do it too!
じゃあ、行きますよー！
Okay, here we go!
チワワじゃないよ！フワワだよ！
I'm not a Chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
フワワじゃないよ！クロちゃんだよ！
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Kuro-chan!
クロちゃんじゃないよ！モココだよ！
I'm not Kuro-chan! I'm Mococo!
3人合わせて...
All 3 of us together...
いやいやいや！ポンポン！
No, no, no! Pon pon!
ちょっと！クロちゃん、出てこないから！なんそれ！
Wait! Kuro-chan, you're not in it! What was that?!
もう、嘘とかつくの良くないよね！
Seriously, telling lies isn't good, is it?!
謝らないと、モココ、パーンチしちゃう！
You have to apologize, or Mococo will punch you!
うわー！いやー！
Whoa! Ya!
救急車、1台...！
Call an ambulance...!
いらないよ！もう嘘...
You don't need one! No more lies...
プンプン！
Hmph, hmph!
落ち着いて、落ち着いて...
Calm down, calm down...
大丈夫、モコちゃん、大丈夫。
It's okay, Moco-chan, it's okay.
クロちゃんはこれからもみんなをいっぱい笑顔にして、素敵なアイドルになってくださいね！
Kuro-chan, please keep making everyone smile and be a wonderful idol!
マジ心...！
Really, from my heart...!
じゃあ、モコちゃん、最後にクロちゃんにハイタッチしてお別れしようね。
So Moco-chan, let's high-five Kuro-chan at the end and say goodbye.
仲直り、仲直り、いい？
Make up, make up, okay?
ハイタッチ、ハイタッチ！
High touch, high touch!
やってみて、やってみて！
Try it, try it!
やだー！
No way~!
バイバイー！
Bye-bye~!
FUWAMOCOちゃん、本当にお誕生日おめでとうございます！
FUWAMOCO, happy birthday to you both!
ありがとうー！
Thank you~!
キュンからのバッキュン！おめでとうハート！
Heartbeat then bang! Congratulations heart!
Let's keep going!
花火！バウバウ！花火、イェーイ！玉屋〜！玉屋〜！
Fireworks! Bau bau! Fireworks, yeah! Tamaya~! Tamaya~!
わぁ〜！
Wow!
Things kind of got really crazy, I'm not too sure what happened...
色々ありすぎて分からなくなってきたかも！
So much happened, I'm starting to get confused!
But we still have one more... One more!
Very exciting tradition, you know! まだまだお楽しみがあるよ！
Very exciting tradition, you know! We still have more fun in store!
Maybe Ruffians, can you guess what it is? 何かな？何かな？
Maybe Ruffians, can you guess what it is? What could it be? What could it be?
FUWAMOCO 1st Anniversary...
We released our 1st...
...1st original song,
"Going to be 1st"!
And then for our 2nd anniversary,
we were able to release "Lifetime Showtime"!
An original song that's grown with us along this journey,
a very special song.
And, you know, for FUWAMOCO,
singing and dancing is something that means so much to us!
Yeah, music!
And Ruffians, might have heard that you'd like to hear more from us too, right?
Right! Yeah!
What do you think? Yeah!
Wow!
Our announcement is...
Drumroll...
Aki-chan drumroll, yes!
Then...
A new original song!
Yeah!
新オリジナル曲！
A new original song!
And this song is extra special!
It's written by none other than the legendary...
...rock idol song composer...
...Matsukuma Kenta-san!
Who's worked with many famous idol groups that we love!
Also written music for the idol group that Kuro-chan produces,
Mameshiba no Taigun-san!
Mameshiba no Taigun!
Yeah!
But Ruffians, you might be a little bit surprised, okay?
So get ready!
Ruffians, with this song...
...we'd like to express...
...our rawest feelings as demon dogs!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
「相棒、どこへ行こうか」 ネオンの脇を抜け
"Partner, where shall we go?" Passing through the neon lights,
バブルガムがはじけたら let's go
once the bubblegum pops, let's go.
最低な夜を潜って僕らは群れをなす
Diving through the worst of nights, we form a pack.
「あの頃よりもマシだね」 my way
"It's better than back then, isn't it?" My way.
「不完全なんです」 首輪をつけた
"We're incomplete," putting on our collars.
良い子なんかじゃもうイヤ ah
We're done playing the good kids, ah!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE 噛みついていけ
DEMON'S RESIDENCE, sink your teeth in!
この街は檻のようで 気分はどうだい 泣いているのかい
This town is like a cage. How do you feel? Are you crying?
鎖をちぎって 叫んでいたんだ stray dogs
Tearing off our chains, we wanted to scream out, stray dogs!
彼方へと飛ぶ鳥を 見上げるだけかい それでいいのかい
Are you just looking up at the birds flying far away? Is that enough for you?
燃えるなら ほら青く
If you're gonna burn, burn bright blue!
「説教なんかいらない」 スプレー缶振って
"We don't need lectures," shaking up the spray can,
イタズラ書きで彩る runway
painting the runway with graffiti.
愛情なんか coin toss 誰に bet するのか
Love is a coin toss—who are you betting on?
不確定要素ばかりね lonely
It's all uncertain variables, lonely.
二人でひとつと決めた
We decided that the two of us are one.
あの目を忘れない ah
I'll never forget those eyes, ah!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE 満天の空
DEMON'S RESIDENCE, under a star-filled sky.
あの星がひどく不快で
Those stars are terribly irritating,
勝利はどうだい 味があるのかい
how does victory taste? Does it have any flavor?
鎖を噛んで 唸っていたんだ stray dogs 僕ら
Biting on our chains, we were growling—stray dogs, that's us.
宇宙さえも撃ち落として
Shooting down even the universe itself,
見下ろす奈落 ビルは輝く
looking down into the abyss as skyscrapers shine.
LOL Now I am free
孤独を分け合い食べた
We shared and swallowed our solitude.
あの目を忘れない
I'll never forget those eyes.
夜を睨んだ stray dogs そうだ
Stray dogs glaring into the night, that's right.
怪物はいずれのほうさ
Which one of us is the real monster?
抜け出せるのかい 足は動くかい
Can you break free? Are your legs moving?
走るならいま
If you're going to run, now's the time!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE stray dogs 僕ら
DEMON'S RESIDENCE, stray dogs, that's us!
この街を駆け抜けて行け
Dash through this town!
地獄の果てに何が見えるかい
What can you see at the end of hell?
鎖をちぎって 叫んでいたんだ stray dogs 僕ら
Tearing off our chains, we were screaming—stray dogs, that's us.
この街は檻のようで
This town is like a cage.
君ならどうだい 共に駆けるかい
How about you? Will you run together with us?
夜明けが合図だ 行こう
Daybreak is the signal—let's go!
Oaff!
Thank you for always being here for us, Ruffians!
Please listen to... side by side!
Finally we made it through but not without some tears
With the help of friends so true we faced all of our fears
Now we're here to celebrate all that we have done
I can feel it's more than just a game of fate
'Cause our stories have just begun
Hand in hand we're not waiting on tomorrow
From now on it's the heart that we will follow
We'll move on past the heartbreak and the sorrow if you
Stay by my side
Dancing harmonies feeding the music as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath the summer sky and through the night
We're making memories every day underneath the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other
Now we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Even though there's been ruff times where nobody wanted us,
We kept going, and we kept dreaming!
Now we're here, we're not alone anymore!
We'll be here together! We have smiles to protect!
C'mon, let's go!
Dancing harmonies feeding the music as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath the summer sky and through the night
We're making memories every day underneath the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other
Now we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Nya-nya-nya, nya-nya-nya...
Oaff!
Thank you for the encore, Ruffians!
That was side by side!
We're really happy to sing side by side for you for the first time live today!
初披露できてとっても嬉しいです！
We're so happy to perform this live for the first time!
side by side is a song made by Aiobahn-san, but also featuring... FUWAMOCO!
We know it's a song that you love a lot, but we also do because...
...it's very special to us, since it's the ending theme for a visual novel that we care about...
NEKOPARA!
And with this song, a dream of singing the opening or ending theme for a visual novel came true!
そう、この楽曲でFUWAMOCOの夢、美少女ゲームの主題歌を歌うことが叶いました！
Yes, with this song, FUWAMOCO's dream of singing a visual novel theme song came true!
A dream came true! Thank you! ありがとう！
A dream came true! Thank you! Thank you!
And thank you so much for joining us for a special day again this year!
It's been a dream, Ruffians!
And you know, it's all because of you that we're able to be here and do all the amazing things that we do, so thank you!
Huh? This next song...
...is our last song?
Aww! But...
...like all of them, it's a very special one!
You know FUWAMOCO are demon guard dogs who are here to protect your smile, right?
We'll continue to do that! Protect your smile! You are our always idols!
And just as I have fluffy and fuzzy souls, too...
We'll continue to be here for thousands and thousands of demon dog years!
Always remembering that, you know, every day isn't given!
Yeah, we don't take anything for granted!
And when you're down, we hope that you'll remember...
...that we're always here cheering you on, okay? We're cheering you on! Love you!
So please listen closely to the lyrics of our last song for today!
明日も 明後日も
Tomorrow, and the day after tomorrow,
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope you'll be smiling...
ずっと... lala...
...forever. Lala...
Thank you so much Ruffians for spending our birthday with us today!
Please think of this song whenever things go wrong, and know that we'll be here!
This last song is for you! Wishful☆Garnet!
過去を振り返ると 思い出す
When I look back at the past, I recall...
ガーネットの空 溢れてく光
...the garnet sky and overflowing light.
この瞳に 映し出された あの日は
That day reflected in these eyes...
美しく 揺れる
...sways beautifully.
What do you think?
紅く 滲んだ 空に
To the sky stained deep red,
願い増した
I made a wish.
どうか この願い
Please, let this wish...
届けてください
...reach you.
明日も 明後日も あなたが笑ってますように
Tomorrow, and the day after, I hope you'll be smiling.
離れ離れになっても 前を向けますように
Even if we are far apart, I hope you can look forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を わたしが壊してあげる
I will break the chains that bind you.
もう 負けないで 進むこと
Don't give up anymore, keep moving forward...
いつでもそばにいるから
...because I will always be by your side.
落ち込んだり自信を無くした時だって
Even when I was feeling down or losing confidence,
目の前にいてくれる
you were right there in front of me.
あなたの笑顔に何度となく 救われた だから
Your smile saved me countlessly, so...
So I love you
挫けそうになったら 手を伸ばして
When you feel like breaking down, reach out your hand.
まだ知らん明日 一緒に見つけよう
Let's discover tomorrow together.
明日も 明後日も あなたを照らしていたい
Tomorrow, and the day after, I want to shine on you.
泣きそうになった時は こっち向いてほしい
When you feel like crying, I want you to look here.
世界でひとりぼっち そんな風に思わないで
Don't ever think you're alone in this world.
愛してくれる人はきっと
The ones who love you...
いつもあなたを想ってる
...are always thinking of you.
Uh... yeah... Wishful☆Garnet
Lala lala... lalala...
願い増した
I made a wish.
どうかこの願い
Please, let this wish...
届けてください！
...reach you!
明日も 明後日も あなたが笑ってますように
Tomorrow, and the day after, I hope you'll be smiling.
離れ離れになっても 前を向けますように
Even if we are far apart, I hope you can look forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を わたしが壊してあげる
I will break the chains that bind you.
もう 負けないで 進むこと
Don't give up anymore, keep moving forward...
輝く空へ
...towards the shining sky.
明日も 明後日も あなたが笑ってますように
Tomorrow, and the day after, I hope you'll be smiling.
離れ離れになっても
Even if we are torn apart,
前を向けますように
I hope you can keep looking forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を
The chains that bind you,
わたしが壊してあげる
I'll break them for you.
もう負けないで進むこと
Don't lose anymore, keep moving forward...
いつでもそばに
Always by your side,
あなたのそばに
By your side,
わたしはいつもいるから
Because I'll always be here.
バウバウ！
Bau bau!
Thank you so much, Ruffians!
We'll see you soon at our encore live in membership, okay?
バウバウ！
Bau bau!
メン限アンコールライブで待ってるよー！
We'll be waiting for you in the membership encore live!